$\left\{ \begin{smallmatrix} \mathsf{G} \\ \mathsf{R} \end{smallmatrix} \right\}$ GIAN RIYANTO

Professional Summary

I am a full-time software engineering student with a knack for technology, appreciation for delightful user experiences, and an obsession for detail. I am in pursuit for new experiences that feed my intellectual curiosity and dedication for learning in order to make meaningful contributions to value-adding products. I seek to continue my learning venture with a team that shares my passion for learning, disruption, and exceptional products.

Personal Info

+61406073200

■ li.griyanto@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/riyantogian

United States Permanent Resident

Australian citizen based in Sydney

Experience

Big Data Engineer

LinkaAja Dec 2019 - Mar 2020

- Proposed and developed an automated data pipeline frameworks using Apache Airflow for improved efficiency and scalability.
- Implemented Direct Acyclic Graphs to schedule and monitor workflows - replacing previously manual and multi-step process.
- Implemented data infrastructure processes to monitor data quality, ensuring production data is accurate and available for key stakeholders and business processes.

SAP SuccessFactors Jr. Consultant

Daya Dimensi Global Nov 2018 - Jun 2019

- Configured SAP SuccessFactors projects based on the client's business process and requirements.
- Gathered, analysed and transformed client needs, insights and problems into tailored system solutions.
- Expressed HCM best practices and related technological implementation.
- Planned, designed, and executed systems integration testing to ensure systems perform in accordance to agreed requirements and customer expectation.

Product and Sales Analyst

Mitra Cipta Agro Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

- Conducted and prepared product and customer research analysis for Southeast Asian market expansion.
- Collaboratively delivered exceptional customer satisfaction through a well orchestrated end-to-end delivery of client Purchase Orders.
- Participated in client sales meetings and delivered customer service duties throughout business delivery process.

Education

University of Technology Sydney

Mar 2016 - Oct 2021

Bachelor of Engineering and Diploma in Professional Engineering Practice (Honours) - **Software Engineering**

Technical Skills

ReactJS, Hooks

VueJS, VueX

Node, Express

HTML, CSS, SCSS

JavaScript

Python

Java

UI/UX Design

Git, Github

Airflow

SQL, NoSQL, MongoDB

Agile Methodology, Scrum

Confluence, Trello, JIRA

Data Analytics

Machine Learning

Interpersonal Skills

Fast and Willing Learner

Inquisitive

Detail-oriented

Adaptable and Flexible

Collaborative

Problem-solving

Software Projects

IOWEYOU Web Application

- Built and deployed a favours-debt-tracking web application using MERN technology stack.
- Worked mostly as a front-end developer designed, developed and delivered an exceptional UI/UX design (received an honourable mention from the professor).
- Practiced writing clean, maintainable, and welldesigned code.

Team Communication Platform

- A team communication channel and project management platform built using ReactJS, Node, and Firebase NoSQL database.
- Collaboratively worked with a team of 15 members using Scrum and Agile practices.

Analytics Dashboard Web Application

- Developed an intuitive and responsive analytics dashboard for users to manage, monitor, and analyse data at a glance.
- Worked as a front-end developer designing and implementing the dashboard interface using VueJS and ChartJS.

Supervised Learning Project

- Implemented a machine learning classification algorithm to predict values of a dataset.
- Employed various data analytics processes, techniques and practices using python to improve efficiency, accuracy and performance.

Automated Data Pipeline

- Developed a data pipeline framework to automate previously laborious multi-step tasks using Python and Apache Airflow.
- Implemented Direct Acyclic Graphs to schedule and monitor workflows that is presently still maintained for various different business use-cases.

Relevant Coursework

Core Engineering Subjects

Design and Innovation
Business Requirements Modelling
Information Systems Development Methodologies
Systems Testing and Quality Management
Entrepreneurship and Commercialisation
Engineering Economics and Finance
Engineering Project Management
Mathematical Modelling 1 & 2

Computer Science Subjects

Advanced Internet Programming
Applications Programming
Data Structures and Algorithms
Introduction to Data Analytics
Database Fundamentals
Object-Relational Database
Software Engineering Studio 1A, 1B, 2A, 2B, 3A
Software Architecture

Other Experiences

Software Engineering Virtual Experience

JPMorgan Chase & Co

Jun 2020 - Jun 2020

Programming Teacher Assistant

Code Camp

Nov 2017 - Nov 2018

Mathematics Teacher Assistant

Montessori Mathematics Tutor

Feb 2012 - Nov 2012

Referees

Rifan Kurnia

Head of Big Data LinkAja

Direct Manager

M 62 8778080480

E rifankurnia@gmail.con

W linkedin.com/in/rifan-kurnia-57743838

Reinaldo Enriko

SAP Consultant HR Path

Supervisor

M 62 82113221162

E reinalod.enriko@gmail.com

W linkedin.com/in/reinaldo-enriko-760a05129

Marcelany

SAP Technical Lead HR Path

Direct Manager

M 62 81183593

E marcelany@ddg.biz

V linkedin.com/in/marcelany